

MARTA PALUSZYŃSKA

designer, UX/UI

I started my professional career as a graphic designed for an advertising agency. Throughout my career I have expanded my skillset, and now, I am a designer in visual communications. My specialities include customer guidance system design in navigating customer experiences in a furniture store. In the near future, I want to further my career and expand as a UX/UI designer. My approach to design is balanced, making sure there is unity and expression in beauty, simplicity and usability.

paluszynska.marta@gmail.com

+48 692 208 062

https://martapaluszynska.github.

EDUCATION

2020 • UX Basic Course EDUWEB

2013-2015 Design master's studies

Academy of Fine Arts in Katowice

2009-2015 Design bachelor studies

UTP University of Science and Technology in Bydgoszcz

WORK EXPERIENCE

od 2017 • Specjalista ds. Ko

Specjalista ds. Komunikacji Wizualnej IKEA Retail SP Z O.O in Katowice

- creating IKEA brand awareness through graphic communication
- informing customers about marketing campaigns,
- planning and implementing customer guidance,
- sales supporting by emphasizing the benefits of products,
- implementation of commercial lighting,
- using large format printers and cutting plotters
- triaining IKEA Co-workers in interpersonal communication

2015-2017

Graphic Designer

X-5 Productions SP Z O.O in Bydgoszcz

- creating event scenery based on license graphics and Key Visuals (Disney, WARNER BROS, Hasbro, Nickelodeon, Animaccord, HiT Entertainment),
- creating posters, banners, leaflets, textile walls, roll-ups,
- creating advertising campaigns for shopping malls,
- visualizations of advertising gadget

Graphic Designer

Milutka in Bydgoszcz

web and social media arts

SKILLS

2d: design and aplication prototyping, vector graphics, raster graphics, logotype design

Adobe Xd,Adobe In Design, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Bridge, Corel, Office 365,

3d: modeling, visualizations, technical documentation, lighting analysing Autodesk Inventor, Autodesk 3ds Max, Solidworks, SketchUp

EXTRA SKILLS/ WORKSHOPS

- teambuilding, group management,
- Teambuilding workshops 2012

2011-2020

VOLOUNTEERING

Scout Guide for The Polish Scouting and Guiding Association

For a number of years, I was heavily involved as a Scout Guide for The Polish Scouting and Guiding Association. As the coordinator for the associations team leaders, I was responsible for, and oversaw the implementation and management of courses and workshops. Including delivering teaching on interpersonal communication and team building. But my fondest memories are of our summer camps with the Brownies group, which I was the leader of.

From my time and participation with the Association, it has equipped me to be able to work in a group environment. And that through team building and cooperation, every problem can be solved!

2016



MARTA PALUSZYŃSKA

projektant, UX/UI

Rozwijam umiejętności w różnych dziedzinach projektowania. Tworzyłam kampanie reklamowe dla hipermarketów i projektowałam scenografie eventów w oparciu o grafiki licencyjne gigantów takich jak Disney czy Warner Bros. Obecnie zajmuję się komunkacją wizualną. W najbliższej przyszłości chcę przenieść moje doświadczenia do świata wirtualnego. Chcę rozpocząć karierę jako projektant UX/UI.

paluszynska.marta@gmail.com

692 208 062

https://martapaluszynska.github.io/

EDUKACJA

2020 • UX Basic Course EDUWEB

2013-2015 • 2° Wzornictwo

Akademia Sztuk Pięknych w Katowicach

2009-2015 • 1° Wzornictwo
Uniwersytet Technologiczno - Przyrodniczy w Bydgoszczy

DOŚWIADCZENIE ZAWODOWE

od 2017

Specjalista ds. Komunikacji Wizualnej

IKEA Retail SP Z O.O w Katowicach

- informowanie klientów o akcjach marketingowych i prezentowanie asortymentu IKEA poprzez komunikację graficzną,
- projektowanie i implementacja komunikacji wizualnej ułatwiającej nawigację po sklepie oraz proces zakupowy,
- wsparcie sprzedaży poprzez podkreślanie benefitów produktów,
- obsuga drukarek wielkoformatowych i ploterów tnących,
- praca z oświetleniem komercyjnym,
- prowadzenie szkoleń dla pracowników IKEA z komunikacji interpersonalnej

2015-2017

Graphic Designer

X-5 Productions SP Z O.O w Bydgoszczy,

- wizualizacje scenografii eventowych w oparciu o grafiki licencyjne i Key Visuale (Disney, WARNER BROS, Hasbro, Nickelodeon, Animaccord, HiT Entertainment).
- przygotowanie plików produkcyjnych scenografii np. ścianki tekstylne, roll-upy, trybunki, elementy frezowane,
- projekty kampanii reklamowych dla sieci hipermarketów,
- przygotowanie materiałów do druku: plakaty, ulotki, banery,
- wizalizacja gadżetów reklamowych
- opracowanie graficzne dokumentów firmy: prezentacje, portfolio itp.

2016

Graphic Designer

Milutka w Bydgoszczy

• grafiki na stronę www i media społecznościowe dla sklepu z akcesoriami dla niemowląt

UMIEJĘTNOŚCI I ZNAJMOŚĆ PROGRAMÓW

2d: Grafika wektorowa, grafika rastrowa, komunikacja wizualna, interfejsy, identyfikacja wizualna, systemy informacji wizualnej Adobe Xd,Adobe In Design, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Bridge, Corel, Office365,

3d: Modelowanie, wizualizacje, dokumentacja techniczna, analiza oświetlenia Autodesk Inventor, Autodesk 3ds Max, Solidworks, SketchUp

DODATKOWE KURSY I UMIEJĘTNOŚCI

- język angielski: poziom intermediate,
- kierowanie grupą, praca w grupie,
- warsztaty Teambuilding 2012,
- prawo jazdy kat. B,
- uprawnienia do obsułgi podestów ruchomych przejezdnych: wolnobieżnych (nożycowych) tzw. "zwyżki".

WOLONTARIAT

2011-2020

Instruktorka Związku Harcerstwa Polskiego w stopniu podharcmistrzyni,

- członkini Zespołu projektowego ds. Zmian instrumentów metodycznych,
- członkini Zespołu Zuchowego Wydziału Wsparcia Metodycznego przy Głównej Kwatrze ZHP
- szefowa zespołu liderów grup młodzieżowych w wieku 6-10lat
- członkini zespołu kształcącego kadrę ZHP

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).